I... I...
I don't want to lose either. To any of you.
This one's mine!
I won...
I actually won!
I...
Good for you, Sis.
Was it fun running with them?
So fun that you forgot about me?
How... could I...
I'm sorry...
I'm a terrible sister.
I could feel my heart pounding...
Even though my heart is supposed to be yours.
I had so much fun... running with them...
I felt so happy!
And because of that...
I forgot... about you.
Hashiridashita hitomi ga
Eyes that being to run,
mezasuno wa ichiban shika nai
aspiring to nothing more than number one
Glorious one moment
shouri de shika tsukamenai kiseki
a miracle that can only achieve victory
Umamusume: Pretty Derby
Road to the Top
Onaji toki wo irodotte
Coloring the very moment,
kagayaki tachi ga jibun wo miteru kara
because the bright lights are looking at me.
Genkai nante kimerarenai
I can't set limits,
unmei ga raibaru
destiny is my rival
Believe Dream
Akogare wa mou chousen ni nattanda
My longing has already become a challenge
Believe Pride
Butai ni tatsun da tte tsuyoi kanjou
I have a strong feeling that I'll be on the stage
Believe Yell
Kotaetai kimochi mo dakishime
Embracing the feeling of wanting to respond
Ima mirai e geeto ga hiraiteku
Now the door of the future opens,
reesu ga hajimatteku
the race begins
Issei taafu ni fuku kaze ni kawaru
It will become the wind blowing on the grass at once
mune no oku no atsui omoi wa
The passion in my heart,
dare ni mo yuzure wa shinai kara
I won't let anyone take it away from me.
Kakenuketeku sokudo wa
The speed at
watashi tachi no sakebi nanda
which we run is our cry
Kisoiau hodo ni hibiiteku
The more we race, the more it resonates
Running to the top!
Eikou to iu gooru e to mukau kiseki
The miracle of running towards the goal of glory
Episode 3: Reason to Run
It's the ocean!
Wow...
It's beautiful... We're getting close to the training campsite.
Yeah! I can't wait!
Me neither!
Top Road-san!
We're here! It's time to get off.
Are you feeling sick from the bus ride?
No, I was just thinking to myself...
I'm okay. Let's go!
It's only the first day.
Why don't you go enjoy yourself for a bit?
No, it's alright.
We're starting with
the sprint, right? I'm good to go!
Ready, and... go!
Her body's too tense—
it's making her form stiffer than usual.
Relax as you run!
Right!
Looks like this is gonna be a tough one.
Um, how was that?
Why don't we call it a day?
Huh? But...
You're only gonna get hurt
if you push yourself too hard.
Let's work on getting our usual pace back.
Oh... I'm sorry.
Rest up tomorrow too.
Take a breather and refresh yourself.
Okay...
Oh, that's super cute!
Let's see. Where else would be nice...
Huh?
Ayabe-san!
Over here! Let's take a picture together!
There's no better time to get a good shot than at sunset!
Ayabe-san?
Leave me alone!
I don't want to take any pictures.
I bet Trainer-san's really disappointed with me...
I should be training harder than ever right now.
I ran my best at the Derby.
But my best wasn't enough.
That’s why I've got to work harder.
I have to keep running...
I'm...
Whoa, Prez!
Sorry!
Are you okay, Prez?
Y-Yes, I'm fine.
By the way,
is this...
Oh.... It was supposed to be a surprise,
but I guess the cat's out of the bag now.
We're making another banner for you.
We wanna really show
our support for the next race!
For me?
Thank you so much.
We're just doing it 'cause we want to!
You're always helping us out
with schoolwork and stuff. It means a lot!
You're amazing, Prez.
You're gonna be great in the next race, I know it!
Thank you so much!
I'll make sure to keep going!
That's our number one prez!
Thanks for helping me fold this back up!
That's right. I have to keep going.
More... More, more, more!
Focus!
One, two. One, two.
Trainer-san told me to take a break...
but I know I have to keep
putting in my best effort!
I won't let everyone down in the next one!
All right. I'll do what I can!
Huh? Hey, look. It's Top Road-san!
Top Road-san!
Did you go to a festival?
Yes.
There was one at a shrine nearby.
Are you in the middle of training?
Nice work!
I want to make sure my performance in the next race is worth watching!
Oh, it always is! You were so close at the Derby!
Yeah... Right.
You're gonna win the next one for sure! So—mrgh!
Um, we bought some fireworks earlier.
Do you want to join us?
Thanks for the invite.
But, I should prepare for tomorrow, so maybe next time!
Top Road-san...
Yum! More please, Rice!
Oh, o-okay.
I guess Ayabe-san's not coming back today either.
It's up to me to stop her tomorrow!
Otherwise...
She's gonna break down...
Good for you, Onee-chan.
You met some worthy rivals, ran with them, and then you basked in the glory of victory.
I'm sorry.
You looked like you were having so much fun.
When I saw how happy you were, I…
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I'm such a horrible sister.
Sorry... I'm so sorry.
I won't... make... the same mistake again.
I wanted her to have some time to cool down...
but I guess she can't help
practicing even while on break.
No use telling her she can't—
that'd just stress her out even more.
Just who are you running for right now?
What to do...
To help her relax, we could...
Wait!
Come to think of it, we're not the only
ones here for a summer training camp.
Umamusume Junior Training Club training camp
Oho.
My, oh, my. What a dilemma.
Whoa! Um... Uh... Wh-What is?
It appears my ambitions are clouding the light of others.
However, I can do naught but wait patiently.
As such, it wouldn't do for her to stop
before she reaches the light in which I stand.
My ambitions are too great to be contained.
They're—
Whoa! I-I'm so sorry! I shouldn't have tossed it around like that!
Handkerchief! We need a handkerchief right away!
Even soda cannot help but overflow before me!
Of course...
In any case, Top Road-san
must shine for both our futures.
Well, that shouldn't be too much of a problem for her.
However, there is one other light I need.
Though, I'm afraid she may be walking too close to the edge.
Hi everyone.
I'm Narita Top Road, your coach for today!
Nice to meet you.
Hello!
Let's get started with some
warm-up exercises, shall we?
Watch closely and try to copy me!
Okay!
Now, first.
Let's check each of your forms by—
Yes, I'd like to see you run, Coach!
Me too!
Sure thing. I'll run a quick lap then!
You're so cool, Coach!
You really went zoooom at the end!
I wanna zoom like that too! How do you do it?
Now, I guess we can practice zooming together!
All right! Get ready to zoom, everyone!
Zoooom!
After we're done eating, we'll be heading to the beach for some more practice!
Okay!
Bye, Coach!
See you next time!
Nice work out there.
Trainer-san!
That suits you a lot more, you know.
Huh?
That smile. It's been a while since I saw it.
What are you talking about?
I've always been smiling.
The camp was a great refresher too...
Is that the truth?
I mean, it has to be... right?
Everyone's cheering me on and telling me
I can win the next one. They all believe in me.
It wouldn't make sense for me to still be down in the dumps.
So I'm fine now. I can—
Then why're you making that face?
Huh?
You're right. I look awful.
I'm no good.
All I do is worry you.
You can worry me all you want.
I'm your trainer, aren't I?
I'm scared... of betraying everyone's trust in me.
What if I lose again?
I don't want to disappoint
all the people cheering me on.
You don't know if you'll lose the next one.
You know better than anyone else that I was in my best condition at the Derby!
Yet... I still lost.
Ever since that day, I can't help but think...
What if I don't improve?
I might never be able to win again.
I want to do my best.
I want to fulfill everyone's expectations of me!
But...
I'm just so scared!
I'm so weak...
I don't deserve their support.
It is not winning...
even after putting in your best effort.
Even so, you haven't said you'll quit.
Even after losing, you continued looking for a way to win.
You put your whole heart into moving forward,
without stopping even once.
You might lose and fall—but you keep on fighting.
That's the Narita Top Road I know.
But... But what if I keep losing?
They won't want to cheer for me anymore...
They will!
Everyone's showing their support because you're Narita Top Road.
You keep fighting... and that's why they'll keep cheering you on.
Trainer-san...
You did well.
I'm...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry you had to see
that embarrassing side of me.
But I feel a bit better...
after crying like that.
Then how about unwinding even more tonight?
Unwinding?
Yep.
Everyone from the shopping
district is here. But why?
When I told them you were feeling down,
they all immediately came out here.
That's right! We heard from the trainer himself!
Don't be a stranger! You tell us when you're feeling blue, you hear?
You guys...
Huh? Your eyes are looking red.
Oh well! The carrots are really sweet, you know.
W-Wait! I'm still...
Let's get some warm food in you!
What took you so long, Prez!
Uh... you are the prez, right?
Fantastic! We just got everything grilled.
Here you go! Some grilled carrot topped with cheese!
This yakisoba here's got a ton of carrot mixed in too!
Everything looks so good!
Ooh, I want some too!
Save some for me! Look at that cheese!
It's amazing.
Have some, Prez!
It does look really good. I'd like some too...
Time to dig in!
Bon appetit.
It's delicious!
This is delicious!
Here, have some of this!
And this too!
You guys... Thank you so much.
No need to thank us.
Everyone loves you, Top Road.
Do your best in the next race too!
Win the preliminary race and get that Kikuka Sho!
You guys...
I guess I didn't need to be so scared after all.
Everyone, you're all cheering me on so wholeheartedly.
I'll do my best.
Very, very best! I'll do nothing but my best!
We get the message, Prez!
Fight on, Top Road!
I'm so happy.
I'll be running against Ayabe-san again at the next GII race...
But I received so much energy
from everyone today.
Now I can keep doing my best!
Sorry... I'm sorry...
You don't have to apologize so much.
You had fun, right?
That's good.
Sorry...
Oh, but that leg is only going to make it to the Kikuka Sho.
Only to the Kikuka Sho?
Does that mean... it's going to break down there?
I always thought it strange.
The doctors told me there was nothing wrong...
But then, why does it hurt so much?
I get it now. So I am getting punished after all.
Fine. You can break it.
If the Kikuka Sho is going
to be my last... then so be it.
The victories, the cheers...
All of it is yours.
I'll win for your sake.
I will... give you everything.
They're rounding the fourth turn.
All that's left is the final sprint to the finish line!
Admire Vega advances to the outside!
She's emerging from the rear and closing in fast!
I knew it'd come to this!
Narita Top Road picks up the pace!
Admire Vega continues charging ahead!
Will this be another Derby?
Ayabe-san's a tough opponent.
She's strong...
but I'm not giving up!
It's not... over yet...
It's not the end!
Narita Top Road is pushing!
She's pushing forward! She's pushing...
but just like at the Derby,
She's not enough to win!
Admire Vega remains victorious!
Oh...
It really did turn out just like the Derby...
Right... It's gotta be tough for Top Road.
Top Road...
No.
It's not over!
After this, I'll talk to Trainer-san about
what I felt were my weak points this time around...
Ayabe-san! Wait.
Narita Top Road... is back to being herself.
Ayabe-san!
I knew it. You're really strong, Ayabe-san.
This is incredibly challenging for me.
That's exactly why...
I'd like to race against you again.
Just wait. I'll run even better at the Kikuka Sho!
Ayabe-san?
I don't care how you run.
All I need to do is win.
Ayabe-san...